{
    "id": "a2e995479503494d909a95629d1a60e5",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This material is different ………………… that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fb92ac078034b91841a28204bb24d3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should explain this ………………… them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5db9a6226e20437e9a15dc88404fa76d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been absent ………………… Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01aaa1413d084f0a9db79b81765821bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t been to the theatre ………………… a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4f6e9c338d3446bbe82995f289ae432"
        },
        {
            "question": "He goes ……………….. school by car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8cf4b369b3f4101849c964c11ec126f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a comfortable house to live ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a9e20506077f4a1b89dc6d5947f64213"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are called …………………. different names.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94fc2f53de6341f4a8bb03fec4476915"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not spend money ………………. luxuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd416d855dbf4d24b606964ded866536"
        },
        {
            "question": "I gave him a chair to sit ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48016f8ebfeb41cfb61d9de864d322ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new term begins …………………. June 1st.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c39887183254388808fdb0de0295482"
        },
        {
            "question": "He poured the tea ………………….. the mug.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf03be112a58427fb6318559fc2272d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he was very pleased …………………. my work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6356680cd125486bafe6b954ab7f135c"
        }
    ]
}